

#### CONTACT ME

miguelseguramx@gmail.com

@miguelseguramx

@miguelseguramx

+52 55 5964 3832

miguelseguramx.com

#### **EDUCATION**

Anthropology FCPyS / UNAM 2019 - 2020

FrontEnd Architecture

Platzi 2019

JavaScript Career

Platzi 2019

**Programming Fundamentals** 

Platzi 2019

English B1 - C1 CELEX / IPN 2016 - 2018

LANGUAGES

English - C1

Spanish - Native

# **MIGUEL ANGEL** SEGURA VAZQUEZ

# FULL STACK DEVELOPER

#### ABOUT ME

I'm a Full Stack Developer with 3 years of experience who loves to get involve in challenging projects where I add value with creativity and my ability to learn.

I like to be very agile and take the initiative to solve problems and take my team to the next level. I am looking to join a team with the same high standards as me.

Likewise, I think that I reflect a lot in my work the values and what I have learned as a Hiker, Dancer, and Bodybuilder.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## Full Stack Developer

LeonidasEsteban.com | September 2020 - Present

I started implementing the UI and my passion for learning and helping other members of the team took me to Design and Implement whole products.

I participated on the launch of 4 different products with different roles, always with ideas that improved our metrics and proposing different sales strategist that improved our earnings over 25%.

As a Software Engineer, I design and implemented API's REST and Pixel Perfected Designs. My contributions automating processes, streamlining workflows and seeking agreements to implement the best solutions, allowed us to reach our objetives very well.

#### Worked with:

React.js

Django

TDD

Next.js

PostgreSQL

Python

• Three.js

Jest

• Serverless Funtions

React Query

Redux

Node.js Figma

 Docker Cypress

### React Developer

KIUX | May 2020 - September 2020

As a React software developer, my responsibilities were migrating a law firm's internal web applications from jQuery and Vanilla JS to React.js, I finished the project two weeks before the deadline and I helped with the redesign of the landing page.

#### Worked with:

- · React.is
- JavaScript
- jQuery